Guide to the Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue Archive MSS.127
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 3: 2000, 58177
  - Subseries 3.1: Administrative Files, 58575
    - Intern Binder: Requests, 1999; 58639 (Box 9, Folder 750)
    - Intern Binder: Orientation Food, 1999; 58638 (Box 9, Folder 751)
    - Intern Binder: Orientation Packets, 1999; 58637 (Box 9, Folder 752)
    - Intern Binder: Space Reservations, 1999; 58636 (Box 9, Folder 753)
    - Intern Binder: Orientation, Plannings, Schedules, 1999; 58635 (Box 9, Folder 754)
    - Intern Orientation, 2000; 58634 (Box 9, Folder 755)
    - Killip Rental Agreement, undated; 58633 (Box 9, Folder 756)
    - Landlord Contact List, undated; 58632 (Box 9, Folder 757)
    - Logistical Notes, 2000; 58631 (Box 9, Folder 758)
    - Meal Plan, undated; 58630 (Box 9, Folder 749)
    - Miscellaneous Notes on Planning, undated; 58629 (Box 9, Folder 760)
    - Other Related Organizations, Sites, undated; 58628 (Box 9, Folder 761)
    - Payment Status of Employees, 2000; 58627 (Box 9, Folder 762)
    - Potential Production/Company/Marketing Assistants, undated; 58626 (Box 9, Folder 763)
    - Presentation Reports, undated; 58625 (Box 9, Folder 764)
    - Press and Marketing Associate, Job Description, 2000; 58624 (Box 9, Folder 765)
    - Press Release, 2000; 58623 (Box 9, Folder 766)
    - Production Contact Information, 2000; 58622 (Box 9, Folder 767)
    - Production Designers, 2000; 58621 (Box 9, Folder 768)
    - Production Directors, 2000; 58620 (Box 9, Folder 769)
    - Productions, Inc., 2000; 58619 (Box 9, Folder 770)
    - Production Ledger, 2000; 58618 (Box 9, Folder 771)
    - Production Manager: Bowin, Monica, 2000; 58617 (Box 9, Folder 772)
    - Production Receipts, 2000; 58616 (Box 9, Folder 773)
    - Production Receipts, 2000; 58615 (Box 9, Folder 774)
    - Production Schedules, 2000; 58614 (Box 9, Folder 775)
    - Props, 2000; 58613 (Box 9, Folder 776)
    - Promotional Materials (Originals), 2000; 58612 (Box 9, Folder 777)
    - Public Relations Candidates, 2000; 58611 (Box 9, Folder 778)
    - Managing Director Application: Jackson, Candace, 2000; 58610 (Box 9, Folder 779)
    - Reflection Week, 2000; 58609 (Box 9, Folder 780)
    - Rental Agreement, undated; 58608 (Box 9, Folder 781)
    - Renter Information Sheet, undated; 58607 (Box 9, Folder 782)
    - Resume for Housing Coordinator: Rebekah Durham, undated; 58606 (Box 9, Folder 783)
    - Review of 1999 Housing Schedule, undated; 58605 (Box 9, Folder 784)
    - Signage, 2000; 58604 (Box 9, Folder 785)
    - Schedule A, Orientation Schedule, 6/26/00, 2000; 58603 (Box 9, Folder 786)
    - Orientation Speech, undated; 58602 (Box 9, Folder 787)
    - Arrival and Departure Schedule, undated; 58601 (Box 9, Folder 788)
    - Sound Studios, 2000; 58600 (Box 9, Folder 789)
    - Space Inventory, 2000; 58599 (Box 9, Folder 790)
    - Spaces, 2000; 58598 (Box 9, Folder 791)
    - Spaces, 2000; 58597 (Box 9, Folder 792)
    - Spaces, Correspondence and Contacts, 2000; 58596 (Box 9, Folder 793)
    - Spaces, Floor Plans and Theater Specs, 2000; 58595 (Box 9, Folder 794)
    - Staff, Miscellaneous Contact Numbers, Resumes, Letters of Reference, undated; 58594 (Box 9, Folder 795)
    - Staff: Waggener, John, 2000; 58593 (Box 9, Folder 796)
    - Staff Meeting Agendas, 2000; 58592 (Box 9, Folder 797)
    - Staff Meetings: June 13-June 30, 2000; 58591 (Box 9, Folder 798)
    - Staff Meetings: July 5-August 1, 2000; 58590 (Box 9, Folder 799)
    - Stage Manager Application: Stephens, Darcy, 2000; 58589 (Box 9, Folder 800)
    - Stage Managers, 2000; 58588 (Box 9, Folder 801)
    - Sublet Information, undated; 58587 (Box 9, Folder 802)
    - Sublet Apt. Notes, 2000; 58586 (Box 9, Folder 803)
    - Summer Participants, 2000; 58585 (Box 9, Folder 804)
    - Telephone Bills, 2000; 58584 (Box 9, Folder 805)
    - Tenant Notes for Each Sublet, undated; 58583 (Box 9, Folder 806)
    - Utility Payments, undated; 58582 (Box 9, Folder 807)
    - Welcome: Transit Maps, undated; 58581 (Box 9, Folder 808)
    - Welcome Letter, 2000; 58580 (Box 9, Folder 809)
    - Welcome Packet Inserts, undated; 58579 (Box 10, Folder 810)
    - Welcome, Safety Packet, 2000; 58578 (Box 10, Folder 811)
    - Welcome to IACD, Summer, 2000; 58577 (Box 10, Folder 812)
    - Welcome: Directory, Contact Sheet, Schedule, undated; 58576 (Box 10, Folder 813)
  - Subseries 3.2: Miscellaneous Project Material, 58558
    These files are assorted records and documentation of the 2000 session projects. Files relate to performers and to pieces. Arranged by topic.
    - Artist Budget: Mosakowski, Susan, 2000; 58574 (Box 10, Folder 814)
    - Artist Budget: Wija, Wayann, undated; 58573 (Box 10, Folder 815)
    - Potential Artists: Brill, Robert, undated; 58572 (Box 10, Folder 816)
    - Artist Budgets, 2000; 58571 (Box 10, Folder 817)
    - Artists Budgets and Proposals, 2000; 58570 (Box 10, Folder 818)
    - Class Action: Budget Proposal, Project Proposal, Press Releases, undated; 58569 (Box 10, Folder 819)
    - Firestones: Hope Azeda, undated; 58568 (Box 10, Folder 820)
    - Gray Matter: Lani Guinier and Tim Mitchell, undated; 58567 (Box 10, Folder 821)
    - Lockdown: Dread Scott, undated; 58566 (Box 10, Folder 822)
    - Ruben Martinez, Border Ballad, undated; 58565 (Box 10, Folder 823)
    - Unfinished Stories: Francesca Harper, Margo Jefferson, Paul Miller, undated; 58564 (Box 10, Folder 824)
    - Musical Prayers: Suzzy and Maggie Roche, undated; 58563 (Box 10, Folder 825)
    - Skin: Patricia Williams and Oliver Lake, undated; 58562 (Box 10, Folder 826)
    - Hymns for Hagar: Ysaye Barnwell, undated; 58561 (Box 10, Folder 827)
    - Grief: Catharine Stimpson, undated; 58560 (Box 10, Folder 828)
    - Press Clippings, 1998-2000, 58559 (Box 10, Folder 829)
  - Subseries 3.3: 2000 Overview, 58524
    Like the 1999 overview in Series 2, this report covers all the activities of the Institute for the Year including profiles of the artists, program operations, schedules of activities as well as administrative details such as fundraising catering arrangements and other logistics. This report is disbound and the sections arranged alphabetically by topic.
    - 2000 Overview: Table of Contents, 58557 (Box 10, Folder 830)
    - Artist Overview: Smith, Anna Deavere, 2000; 58556 (Box 10, Folder 831)
    - Artist Overview: Smith, Anna Deavere, 2000; 58555 (Box 10, Folder 832)
    - Artist Overview: Alfaro Luis and Aguilar, Laura, 2000; 58554 (Box 10, Folder 833)
    - Artist Overview: Barnwell, Ysaye, 2000; 58553 (Box 10, Folder 834)
    - Artist Overview: Harper, Francesca and Jefferson, Margo, 2000; 58552 (Box 10, Folder 835)
    - Artist Overview: Kennedy, Sheila, 2000; 58551 (Box 10, Folder 836)
    - Artist Overview: Martinez, Ruben, 2000; 58550 (Box 10, Folder 837)
    - Artist Overview: Roche, Suzzy, 2000; 58549 (Box 10, Folder 838)
    - Artist Overview: Scott, Dread, 2000; 58548 (Box 10, Folder 839)
    - Artist Overview: Williams, Patricia, 2000; 58547 (Box 10, Folder 840)
    - Artists' Projects, 2000; 58546 (Box 10, Folder 841)
    - Appointment Information, 2000; 58545 (Box 10, Folder 842)
    - Artist and Staff Positions, 2000; 58544 (Box 10, Folder 843)
    - Barker Center Floorplans, 2000; 58543 (Box 10, Folder 844)
    - Budget and Map of Sub-activities, 2000; 58542 (Box 10, Folder 845)
    - Company Management, 2000; 58541 (Box 10, Folder 846)
    - Contact Information and Schedules, 2000; 58540 (Box 10, Folder 847)
    - Core Audiences, 2000; 58539 (Box 10, Folder 848)
    - Dread Scott--Search for Assistant, 2000; 58538 (Box 10, Folder 849)
    - Dunster St. Tasks, 2000; 58537 (Box 10, Folder 850)
    - Financial Information, 2000; 58536 (Box 10, Folder 851)
    - Housing, 2000; 58535 (Box 10, Folder 852)
    - Menus, 2000; 58534 (Box 10, Folder 853)
    - Office Equipment, 2000; 58533 (Box 10, Folder 854)
    - Payments and Appointments, 2000; 58532 (Box 10, Folder 855)
    - Production Space, 2000; 58531 (Box 10, Folder 856)
    - Resumes, 2000; 58530 (Box 10, Folder 857)
    - Staff Meetings/Agendas June 12-June 16, 2000; 58529 (Box 10, Folder 858)
    - Participants, 2000; 58528 (Box 10, Folder 859)
    - Projects for Summer, 2000; 58527 (Box 10, Folder 860)
    - Northern Lights--Video, 2000; 58526 (Box 10, Folder 861)
    - Web Page Information, 2000; 58525 (Box 10, Folder 862)
  - Subseries 3.4: Appointment Protocol, 58517
    This small group of files were received as an isolated group and all concern the appointment of artists for the summer of 2000. The files are arranged by topic.
    - Diamond, Liz: Call to Artists Correspondence, undated; 58523 (Box 10, Folder 863)
    - "Yes" List of 2000 Artist Applicants, 58522 (Box 10, Folder 864)
    - Artist Finalists for Summer 2000, 58521 (Box 10, Folder 865)
    - Call to Artists, 2000; 58520 (Box 10, Folder 866)
    - "Thank You" to Applicants, undated; 58519 (Box 10, Folder 867)
    - Miscellaneous, undated; 58518 (Box 10, Folder 868)
  - Subseries 3.5: Artist Applications--Appointed, 58480
    Applications of the artists who received appointment for 2000, arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Acosta, Julian, undated; 58516 (Box 10, Folder 869)
    - Alfaro, Luis, undated; 58515 (Box 10, Folder 870)
    - Alguilar, Laura, undated; 58514 (Box 10, Folder 871)
    - Azeda, Hope, undated; 58513 (Box 10, Folder 872)
    - Barnwell, Ysaye, undated; 58512 (Box 10, Folder 873)
    - Bell, Mercy, undated; 58511 (Box 10, Folder 874)
    - Bowers, Bill, undated; 58510 (Box 10, Folder 875)
    - Campbell, Colin, undated; 58509 (Box 10, Folder 876)
    - Caraway, Nancie, undated; 58508 (Box 10, Folder 877)
    - Chae, Esther, undated; 58507 (Box 10, Folder 878)
    - Coleman, Chad, undated; 58506 (Box 10, Folder 879)
    - Cummings. Blondell, undated; 58505 (Box 10, Folder 880)
    - DuPre, Lynette, undated; 58504 (Box 10, Folder 881)
    - Fleschler, Glen, undated; 58503 (Box 10, Folder 882)
    - Foster, Gloria, undated; 58502 (Box 10, Folder 883)
    - Harper, Francesca, undated; 58501 (Box 10, Folder 884)
    - Jefferson, Margo, undated; 58500 (Box 10, Folder 885)
    - Kanakulya, Freddie, undated; 58499 (Box 10, Folder 886)
    - Kennedy, Sheila, undated; 58498 (Box 10, Folder 887)
    - Kondo, Dorinne, undated; 58497 (Box 10, Folder 888)
    - Lake, Oliver, undated; 58496 (Box 10, Folder 889)
    - Lee, Charlie, undated; 58495 (Box 10, Folder 890)
    - Lichtman, Amos, undated; 58494 (Box 10, Folder 891)
    - Martinez, Ruben, undated; 58493 (Box 10, Folder 892)
    - Ping Chong and Co., undated; 58492 (Box 10, Folder 893)
    - Ramirez, Sarah, undated; 58491 (Box 10, Folder 894)
    - Reynolds, Todd, undated; 58490 (Box 10, Folder 895)
    - Riddle, Kimber, undated; 58489 (Box 10, Folder 896)
    - Roche, Maggie, undated; 58488 (Box 10, Folder 897)
    - Roche, Suzzy, undated; 58487 (Box 10, Folder 898)
    - Saul, Abdoulage, undated; 58486 (Box 10, Folder 899)
    - Scott, Dread, undated; 58485 (Box 10, Folder 900)
    - Tully, Patrick, undated; 58484 (Box 10, Folder 901)
    - Warring, Stacy, undated; 58483 (Box 10, Folder 902)
    - Welch, David, undated; 58482 (Box 10, Folder 903)
    - Williams, Patricia, undated; 58481 (Box 10, Folder 904)
  - Subseries 3.6: Artist Applications--Tentative, 58434
    These applicants passed an initial screening and include applications from people who did finally participate in the Institute. Files are arranged alphabetically by applicant's last name.
    - Arner, David, undated; 58479 (Box 11, Folder 905)
    - Belluso, John, undated; 58478 (Box 11, Folder 906)
    - Borca, Karen, undated; 58477 (Box 11, Folder 907)
    - Bullins, Ed, undated; 58476 (Box 11, Folder 908)
    - Canner, Elizabeth, undated; 58475 (Box 11, Folder 909)
    - Catler, John, undated; 58474 (Box 11, Folder 910)
    - Chuma, Yoshiko, undated; 58473 (Box 11, Folder 911)
    - Collins, Mary, undated; 58472 (Box 11, Folder 912)
    - Conway, Mary, undated; 58471 (Box 11, Folder 913)
    - Cooper, Mark, undated; 58470 (Box 11, Folder 914)
    - Crockford, Michael, undated; 58469 (Box 11, Folder 915)
    - Davis, Joe, undated; 58468 (Box 11, Folder 916)
    - Denes, Agnes, undated; 58467 (Box 11, Folder 917)
    - Evans, Josef, undated; 58466 (Box 11, Folder 918)
    - Fisk, Roger, undated; 58465 (Box 11, Folder 919)
    - Fo, Dario, undated; 58464 (Box 11, Folder 920)
    - Grubbs, Carl, undated; 58463 (Box 11, Folder 921)
    - DeGarma, Mark, undated; 58462 (Box 11, Folder 922)
    - El-Dabh, Halim, undated; 58461 (Box 11, Folder 923)
    - Greenway, Greg, undated; 58460 (Box 11, Folder 924)
    - Ho, Fred, undated; 58459 (Box 11, Folder 925)
    - Hovland, Patricia, undated; 58458 (Box 11, Folder 926)
    - Jacobson-Hardy, Michael, undated; 58457 (Box 11, Folder 927)
    - Katz, Joel, undated; 58456 (Box 11, Folder 928)
    - 127.0002, Strange Fruit by Joel Katz, undated; 58455 (Box 11, Folder 928a)
      Video recording, VHS, JVC T-120SX (on box) T30 (on cassette) Strange Fruit--Sample Reel; RT 11:20, Produced/Directed by Joel Katz, undated.
    - Knaack, Donald, undated; 58454 (Box 11, Folder 929)
    - Kim-Gibson, Dai, undated; 58453 (Box 11, Folder 930)
    - Lacy, Suzanne, undated; 58452 (Box 11, Folder 931)
    - Lewis, George, undated; 58451 (Box 11, Folder 932)
    - Lewis, Victoria Ann, undated; 58450 (Box 11, Folder 933)
    - Maroney, Denman, undated; 58449 (Box 11, Folder 934)
    - Mason, Keith Antar, undated; 58448 (Box 11, Folder 935)
    - McCallum, Bradley, undated; 58447 (Box 11, Folder 936)
    - Mosakowski, Susan, undated; 58446 (Box 11, Folder 937)
    - Neblett, Tommy, undated; 58445 (Box 11, Folder 938)
    - Parris-Bailey, Linda, undated; 58444 (Box 11, Folder 939)
    - Rahman, Aishah, undated; 58443 (Box 11, Folder 940)
    - Rahmani, Aviva, undated; 58442 (Box 11, Folder 941)
    - Speranza, Carolyn, undated; 58441 (Box 11, Folder 942)
    - Swanson, Christopher, undated; 58440 (Box 11, Folder 943)
    - Washington, Lula, undated; 58439 (Box 11, Folder 944)
    - Wayan, Wija, undated; 58438 (Box 11, Folder 945)
    - Xiang, Jin, undated; 58437 (Box 11, Folder 946)
    - XYZ, Emily, undated; 58436 (Box 11, Folder 947)
    - Yankowitz, Susan, undated; 58435 (Box 11, Folder 948)
  - Subseries 3.7: Artist Applications--Rejected and Tentative Rejections, 58210
    The applicants were either rejected outright or invited to participate in the Institute in non-funded roles. Files are arranged alphabetically by applicant last name.
    - "Rejected" and "Invited to Partake Without Funding" Categories, 2000; 58433 (Box 11, Folder 949)
    - Abbondanzo, Annette, 2000; 58432 (Box 11, Folder 950)
    - Afro-Bradley, Henry, 2000; 58431 (Box 11, Folder 951)
    - Allen, Alistair, 2000; 58430 (Box 11, Folder 952)
    - Allen, Eddie, 2000; 58429 (Box 11, Folder 953)
    - Aree, Elia, 2000; 58428 (Box 11, Folder 954)
    - Atwood, Donald, 2000; 58427 (Box 11, Folder 955)
    - Azeda, Hope, 2000; 58426 (Box 11, Folder 956)
    - Banks, William Jr., 2000; 58425 (Box 11, Folder 957)
    - Barancik, Bob, 2000; 58424 (Box 11, Folder 958)
    - Benary, Barbara, 2000; 58423 (Box 11, Folder 959)
    - Bersley, Tracy, 2000; 58422 (Box 11, Folder 960)
    - Bissundyal, Churaumanie, 2000; 58421 (Box 11, Folder 961)
    - Blockstein, Mike, 2000; 58420 (Box 11, Folder 962)
    - Bobgan, Raymond, 2000; 58419 (Box 11, Folder 963)
    - Bower, Sam, 2000; 58418 (Box 11, Folder 964)
    - Brooking, Bertelle, 2000; 58417 (Box 11, Folder 965)
    - Brown, Guillermo, 2000; 58416 (Box 11, Folder 966)
    - Brown, Kirk, 2000; 58415 (Box 11, Folder 967)
    - Bulik, Robert, 2000; 58414 (Box 11, Folder 968)
    - Burgess, Martha, 2000; 58413 (Box 11, Folder 969)
    - Butler, Eugenia, 2000; 58412 (Box 11, Folder 970)
    - Carly, Lauren, 2000; 58411 (Box 11, Folder 971)
    - Cavalieri, Grace, 2000; 58410 (Box 11, Folder 972)
    - Cebulska, Marcia, 2000; 58409 (Box 11, Folder 973)
    - Chodhourre. Eugenia, 2000; 58408 (Box 11, Folder 974)
    - Chang, Anita, 2000; 58407 (Box 11, Folder 975)
    - Choy, Anita, 2000; 58406 (Box 11, Folder 976)
    - Chutiwongpati, Sarawut, 2000; 58405 (Box 11, Folder 977)
    - Coffing-Blain, Crista, 2000; 58404 (Box 11, Folder 978)
    - Cook, Kim, 2000; 58403 (Box 11, Folder 979)
    - Corbin, Jeri, 2000; 58402 (Box 11, Folder 980)
    - Cunningham, Al, 2000; 58401 (Box 11, Folder 981)
    - Cunningham, Kevin, 2000; 58400 (Box 11, Folder 982)
    - Cuomo, Chris, 2000; 58399 (Box 11, Folder 983)
    - Curran, K.T., 2000; 58398 (Box 11, Folder 984)
    - Dannenfelsen, David, 2000; 58397 (Box 11, Folder 985)
    - Davis, Eisa, 2000; 58396 (Box 11, Folder 986)
    - Davol, Sarah, 2000; 58395 (Box 11, Folder 987)
    - Denison, Hannah, 2000; 58394 (Box 11, Folder 988)
    - Dickson, Josie, 2000; 58393 (Box 11, Folder 989)
    - DiStefano, Joan, 2000; 58392 (Box 11, Folder 990)
    - Dominguez, Ricardo, 2000; 58391 (Box 11, Folder 991)
    - Driscoll, Mary, 2000; 58390 (Box 11, Folder 992)
    - Duncan, Alan, 2000; 58389 (Box 11, Folder 993)
    - Duffield, Margie, 2000; 58388 (Box 11, Folder 994)
    - Dutz, Bradley, 2000; 58387 (Box 11, Folder 995)
    - Echanique, Melisande, 2000; 58386 (Box 11, Folder 996)
    - Eder, Melissa, 2000; 58385 (Box 11, Folder 997)
    - Eis, Joel, 2000; 58384 (Box 11, Folder 998)
    - Farrell, Mia, 2000; 58383 (Box 11, Folder 999)
    - Fitzner-Atchison, Judy, 2000; 58382 (Box 11, Folder 1000)
    - Flax, John, 2000; 58381 (Box 11, Folder 1001)
    - Fox, Jonathan, 2000; 58380 (Box 11, Folder 1002)
    - Franklin, Ife, 2000; 58379 (Box 11, Folder 1003)
    - Friedman, Gary, 2000; 58378 (Box 11, Folder 1004)
    - Frillman, Karen, 2000; 58377 (Box 11, Folder 1005)
    - Gaiter, Collette, 2000; 58376 (Box 11, Folder 1006)
    - Gallimard, Gwylene, 2000; 58375 (Box 11, Folder 1007)
    - Giering, Jennifer, 2000; 58374 (Box 11, Folder 1008)
    - Goggin, Nan, 2000; 58373 (Box 11, Folder 1009)
    - Graham, Lonnie, 2000; 58372 (Box 11, Folder 1010)
    - Gordin, Ain, 2000; 58371 (Box 11, Folder 1011)
    - Greanier, Mary-Ann, 2000; 58370 (Box 11, Folder 1012)
    - Greenfield, Elena, 2000; 58369 (Box 11, Folder 1013)
    - Gross, June; Novosielski, Viesia, 2000; 58368 (Box 11, Folder 1013)
    - Gross, Sally; Norvell, Patsy, 2000; 58367 (Box 11, Folder 1014)
    - Gundersheimer, Lee, 2000; 58366 (Box 11, Folder 1015)
    - Hakoshimanm, Yass, 2000; 58365 (Box 11, Folder 1016)
    - Hamilton, Ann; Harper, Francesca, 2000; 58364 (Box 11, Folder 1018)
    - Hammers, Dawna, 2000; 58363 (Box 11, Folder 1019)
    - Hardenbergh, Marylee, 2000; 58362 (Box 12, Folder 1020)
    - 127.0003, Marylee Hardenbergh: Performance Art/Choreography, undated; 58361 (Box 12, Folder 1020a)
      Video recording, VHS, Sony T-120. Marylee Hardenbergh: Performance Art/Choreography; includes four pieces: "Bobcat Dance", "Plant Dance", "A Dance for Peace", and "Bridge Dancing"; RT 15:36; undated.
    - Haycock, Brooke, 2000; 58360 (Box 12, Folder 1021)
    - Heffernan, Maureen, 2000; 58359 (Box 12, Folder 1022)
    - Henes, Donna, 2000; 58358 (Box 12, Folder 1023)
    - Hill, Morton, 2000; 58357 (Box 12, Folder 1024)
    - Hooker, William, 2000; 58356 (Box 12, Folder 1025)
    - Horban, Jamie, 2000; 58355 (Box 12, Folder 1026)
    - Houston, Sterling, 2000; 58354 (Box 12, Folder 1027)
    - Houston, Velina, 2000; 58353 (Box 12, Folder 1028)
    - Huisman, Frans, 2000; 58352 (Box 12, Folder 1029)
    - Innevarity, Mermie, 2000; 58351 (Box 12, Folder 1030)
    - Inuzuka, Sadashi, 2000; 58350 (Box 12, Folder 1031)
    - Jackson, Homer, 2000; 58349 (Box 12, Folder 1032)
    - Jackson, Shawn D., 2000; 58348 (Box 12, Folder 1033)
    - Jang, Jon, 2000; 58347 (Box 12, Folder 1034)
    - Johnson, Stephanie, 2000; 58346 (Box 12, Folder 1035)
    - Jones, Daniel, 2000; 58345 (Box 12, Folder 1036)
    - Jones, Katherine, 2000; 58344 (Box 12, Folder 1037)
    - Kalisher, Jesse, 2000; 58343 (Box 12, Folder 1038)
    - Kalu, Uchechi, 2000; 58342 (Box 12, Folder 1039)
    - Kaminsky, Sheila; Hedman, Norman, 2000; 58341 (Box 12, Folder 1040)
    - Kamler, Richard, 2000; 58340 (Box 12, Folder 1041)
    - Keefe, Moira, 2000; 58339 (Box 12, Folder 1042)
    - Kelly, Nancy, 2000; 58338 (Box 12, Folder 1043)
    - Kelson, Carolyn, 2000; 58337 (Box 12, Folder 1044)
    - Kempe, Kelly, 2000; 58336 (Box 12, Folder 1045)
    - Khaminna, Muhonjia, 2000; 58335 (Box 12, Folder 1046)
      Contains one 3.5x3.5 diskette labeled as containing the artist's resume and statement of intent.
    - Kim-Gibson, Dai Sil, 2000; 58334 (Box 12, Folder 1047)
    - Kingsbury, Lonna, 2000; 58333 (Box 12, Folder 1048)
    - Kirkwood, Carla, 2000; 58332 (Box 12, Folder 1049)
    - Klugherz, Alice Jane, 2000; 58331 (Box 12, Folder 1050)
    - Krebs, Joey, 2000; 58330 (Box 12, Folder 1051)
    - Kreitzer, Carson Sarah, 2000; 58329 (Box 12, Folder 1052)
    - Krusczewska, Meg, 2000; 58328 (Box 12, Folder 1053)
    - LaPlante, Skip, 2000; 58327 (Box 12, Folder 1054)
    - Lark, Carol; Bernstein, Mary, 2000; 58326 (Box 12, Folder 1055)
    - Lascari, Anna, 2000; 58325 (Box 12, Folder 1056)
    - Lee, Belinda, 2000; 58324 (Box 12, Folder 1057)
    - Leiven-Young, Mark, 2000; 58323 (Box 12, Folder 1058)
    - Leonard, Xavier, 2000; 58322 (Box 12, Folder 1059)
    - Le Schhorn, Dick, 2000; 58321 (Box 12, Folder 1060)
    - Levno, Stacey, 2000; 58320 (Box 12, Folder 1061)
    - Lodato, Victor, 2000; 58319 (Box 12, Folder 1062)
    - Lowenstern, Michael, 2000; 58318 (Box 12, Folder 1063)
    - Macafee, Norman, 2000; 58317 (Box 12, Folder 1064)
    - Mack, Evan, 2000; 58316 (Box 12, Folder 1065)
    - MacLow, Clarinda, 2000; 58315 (Box 12, Folder 1066)
    - Mancini, Ogostino, 2000; 58314 (Box 12, Folder 1067)
    - 127.0004, Let Us Put Our Minds Together Music CD, 1997; 58313 (Box 12, Folder 1067a)
      Sound recording, compact disk, Let Us Put Our Minds Together by The Hawk Project; c1997, published by Yerry Music Publishing, RT approx. 50 min. Modern arrantgements of traditional Native American songs.
    - Mann, Chris, 2000; 58312 (Box 12, Folder 1068)
      One completely unlabeled, uncased, compact disk interleaved in book.
    - Mannix, Edward, 2000; 58311 (Box 12, Folder 1069)
    - Manriquez, L. Frank, 2000; 58310 (Box 12, Folder 1070)
    - Martin, Dan, 2000; 58309 (Box 12, Folder 1071)
    - Martinez, Daniel, undated; 58308 (Box 12, Folder 1072)
    - Martinez, Thea, undated; 58307 (Box 12, Folder 1073)
    - McGaughey, Stanley, undated; 58306 (Box 12, Folder 1074)
    - McGruder, Jasper, undated; 58305 (Box 12, Folder 1075)
    - McLoughlin, Cathleen, undated; 58304 (Box 12, Folder 1076)
    - McNeely, Madeleine, undated; 58303 (Box 12, Folder 1077)
    - Medley, Cassandra, undated; 58302 (Box 12, Folder 1078)
    - Misurell-Mitchell, Janice, undated; 58301 (Box 12, Folder 1079)
    - Mitchell, James, undated; 58300 (Box 12, Folder 1080)
    - Morris, Bonnie, undated; 58299 (Box 12, Folder 1081)
    - 127.0005, Race, Prejudice and Health Care, undated; 58298 (Box 12, Folder 1081a)
      Sound recording, audiocassettes, Brand/type unknown. Race, Prejudice and Health Care: The Lessons of the Tuskegee Syphilis Experiment; set of four audiocassettes of a seminar sponsored by the Urban Coalition, Illusion Theater, and the Center for Biomedical Ethics of the University of Minnesota. Undated, running time unknown. Submitted as part of the application of Bonnie Morris.
    - Oson, Nadine, undated; 58297 (Box 12, Folder 1082)
    - Morett, Maria, undated; 58296 (Box 12, Folder 1083)
    - Mosley, April, undated; 58295 (Box 12, Folder 1084)
    - Nava, Silvia, undated; 58294 (Box 12, Folder 1085)
    - Newman, Jeremy, undated; 58293 (Box 12, Folder 1086)
    - Nickeson, Sandra, undated; 58292 (Box 12, Folder 1087)
    - Panek, Peter, undated; 58291 (Box 12, Folder 1088)
    - Papadakos, Ana, undated; 58290 (Box 12, Folder 1089)